WWW.MY-SUBS.CO
Now's the time. At 3:00 p.m.,
the suite will be empty.
The code to the safe is 1026.
You can get back everything
that was stolen from you.
_
- Aloha, Pattons.
I came by your office last night,
but you were occupied.
Did you get a chance
to look at the proposal?
Greg is at the bar,
and he says he's waiting for me.
That is... That's not gonna... stay...
You're such a gorgeous couple,
so be happy, okay?
Be happy, Rachel.
I think I've made a terrible mistake.
I'm not in the mood anymore.
I'm tired of being
the fucking punching bag!
Don't hurt me, don't hurt me...
_
- Synced and corrected by Darrow -
- www.MY-SUBS.com -
Wake up, you dumb fucker!
What, you homeless?
Let's go, brother. We need you.
Don't keep us waiting, you fucker!
Don't tip our shit over, bro.
Hey, baba.
Baba, you wanna get some brekkie?
Rach?
I booked a facial for this morning.
_
What are you doing?
Texting.
Texting who?
My sister.
Is there a problem?
I don't know. Is there?
No.
No way. Oh, my God.
Hmm.
This is why people go on vacation.
You were amazing.
Yesterday. Superman in a scuba suit.
My hero.
Thank you.
♪ Here I come to save the day ♪
Oh, my God.
Oh, boy...
- Hi.
You were on fire last night.
I was?
Yeah, you were hilarious.
You tried to get me to throw
your dead mother's ashes in the trash.
Oh, my God.
- Did you?
- No.
You really let it all hang out.
I'm okay.
Hey, they put out some fresh kiwi.
- Oh.
- I got you some.
- Oh, thank you, Mark.
- I know how you love it.
I do. Oh, I love this kiwi.
Try one.
Mm, mm, so sweet.
- Oh, my God.
- So sweet here.
What?
Mr. and Mrs. Mossbacher,
how are you? Are you all right?
Our deepest apologies again.
And I do hope you find a way
to enjoy the rest of your trip.
Uh, I heard you're taking out
the dive boat again today.
That should be diverting.
Morning, ladies.
Did you find our medications?
Afraid not.
Enjoy.
- Thank you.
- Thanks.
Thank you.
Hey, can I get a coffee, black?
- Of course.
- Black coffee? Great.
Hey, nice shiner.
- Ah.
- How'd that happen?
You should see the other guy.
Yeah.
No, seriously.
Yeah, we were going scuba diving,
my son and I.
We got our PADI licenses in the pool.
And the girls and I were gonna go, too,
you know,
just have a nice day on the boat.
And I decided last minute not to go.
So, I was up in the room
straightening up.
And then out of nowhere,
this guy jumps out.
He was in the room
trying to steal my stuff,
trying to steal our jewels.
They were in the safe.
So, he had gotten into the safe somehow.
He threw me to the ground so violently.
That's when I walked in.
He doesn't see me, right?
He has on his scuba suit.
I thought you might like
some water while you're waiting.
- Thank you.
- Of course.
Thanks.
Your facialist should be out any minute.
Great.
Thanks.
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Anything I can do?
No, thank you, though.
Actually, do you know if there's
any rooms available tonight?
I just work at the spa,
but I'm happy to call.
No, no, no, no, that's fine. Don't.
I just was curious,
you know, just in case.
It's not a big deal.
Just, my marriage, you know, whatever.
This is my card.
That's my cell.
Um, call me if you need anything.
It's Belinda.
Thank you.
Mrs. Patton, I'm ready for you.
Where have you been, man?
I was on the canoe.
We went all around the island.
It was cool.
Well, you missed breakfast.
And in an hour, we're going scuba.
I'm pretty beat.
Uh, my arms are like numb.
Well, we still gotta scuba.
It's the last day we can do it.
Why?
'Cause we go home tomorrow.
Oh.
I'm thinking I'm not going home.
Yeah, I think I wanna stay here.
The guys need a sixth for their crossing
'cause the guy
that they've been training with,
he keeps flaking 'cause he's a drunk.
And in the spring,
we're all gonna do a Hokule'a
through all of Polynesia,
which sounds amazing.
Honey, you're not going on that.
You're 16. You're in school.
School's easy. I can just finish online.
This is absurd.
What about your life at home?
What life at home?
What about us, your family?
Come visit.
Wait. I can't tell
if you're being serious.
I'm very serious.
Quinn, is this about your phone?
Because we wouldn't have
your new phone shipped here?
- No.
- Because relax,
it's gonna be there when we get home.
What? Mom, I don't care about a phone.
I don't even want a phone.
Well, you're getting a phone.
You're not gonna not have a phone.
This is ridiculous.
Look, staying here without us,
not an option, no.
I support you, Quinn.
Live your dream. Paddle to Fiji.
Shane.
Shane?
Not yet, he gave me a bullshit number.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah, that'd be great.
No, I know.
Dude, trust me, I know.
I'm going to call Randy Zeoli right now.
Well, good. Go scalp some heads.
- You know I will.
- All right, Lorenzo.
- I'll call you back.
- Thanks.
It's my mom's travel agent.
The dude is hardcore.
He knows one of the owners of the hotel.
He's gonna call. He's gonna raise hell.
Why?
Why? Listen to this.
Okay, you know the family
that arrived on the boat with us,
the ones you think are weird?
They went back to their room yesterday,
and there's like a jewel thief
in their fucking bedroom.
- What?
- Yeah.
There's like a fight and everything,
and then the guy takes all their stuff.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, he had a key to the room.
The only reason I know about this
is 'cause the dad had a shiner
and I asked him about it.
The hotel didn't tell us shit.
Like, if he's got a key to their room,
he could have a key to our room.
Like, who fucking knows?
- It's freaky.
- I'm serious.
We are in the biggest suite
at the hotel.
We could be a target.
I just wish I had a gun
or like a baseball bat at least,
or something.
You know, like, fucking...
Hmm. Yes!
Hold on.
That's the knife they gave us
to cut the pineapples.
What, are you gonna cut
a bunch of pineapples?
Gonna keep this by the bed.
Gotta protect my hot wife.
This Armond guy is unbelievable.
He's going down.
Shane.
Lorenzo's all over it.
Oh, how was your facial?
Your face looks nice and shiny.
Shane.
What?
I...
I can't believe
that I'm saying this, but, uh...
I think I made a mistake.
What's the mistake?
The mistake is...
the mistake is...
getting married...
to you.
What?
Shane, when I met you,
I was... in a weird place.
And, uh...
I had my bad breakup,
and work was so frustrating.
And...
And then you came along,
and you're so handsome,
and I was so attracted to you,
and you had so much going on, and...
going around the city with you
was like a fantasy.
All the doors opened,
and then you asked me
to marry you, and...
And look, I admit,
when I was little,
I had princess dolls, and...
I was a girly girl and I dreamt
about my wedding day
and... and Prince Charming
and all that shit.
What the fuck are you talking about?
- And then I...
- Are you for real right now?
And then I got caught up in the wedding,
and that was the last five months,
basically.
And everyone, you know, I could tell
thought I was so lucky,
and that made me feel good.
But like in the dumbest way.
Because...
Because now I'm here and...
And what?
And...
I realize...
I don't wanna be a plus one
my whole life.
Okay, so don't be.
I mean, I'm not telling you
to be anything.
But that's just how it is.
Okay, so are you blaming me
'cause you're not more successful?
No, I'm not blaming you for anything.
You've done nothing wrong.
What a relief. Like...
After I've wined you and dined you
and asked you to marry me,
and then made you the center of my life,
it's just nice to know
you're not pissed.
Shane, this is about me.
I'm not okay with being a trophy wife,
an appendage like all these
other women in your world.
Okay, so you're pretty
and that's part of the appeal for me,
and what, that bothers you?
I just need to respect myself.
I gotta hand it to you. Ah... You...
You hid yourself really well, Rachel.
I mean, this whole time,
I bought that you were this cool chick
who was fun and confident and normal.
And I had no idea that you were
this insecure, naive baby.
You're the baby, Shane.
Coddled by your mommy,
who showed up on your honeymoon.
You don't get the room you want,
so you throw a never-ending tantrum.
I genuinely cannot believe
what a baby-man you can be.
Okay, I'm out.
I'm gonna go for a swim.
Because now,
we are starting down a very dark road,
and you better be sure
you really wanna go there.
Mossbachers!
Oh, I was hoping to catch you.
I have good news.
I received a call, and the stolen items,
all your jewelry,
it's all been recovered.
- Oh, that's great.
- Fantastic.
There's some sort of process,
but I made them promise
to give everything back to you
before your departure tomorrow.
So, they found the guy?
They did.
Was it an employee?
It was.
Look, on behalf of the hotel,
I just wanna say I am so sorry.
What's his name?
Kai.
And it's so strange,
'cause he was such a sweet kid.
And I never had a problem with him ever.
I never would've guessed him
in a million years.
Well, uh, I just wanted to give you
the good news about your jewelry.
And I hope you have an incredible dive.
- Thanks.
- Thank you. It's great news.
It is, yes. Happy for you.
How's it going?
It's hot today.
What's good?
Mm.
Sorry, that chaise is taken.
But you're a very pretty man.
Okay.
Oh, yeah.
All right.
You know, I could rent a house in Aspen.
You live near there, right?
That's if you wanna keep
the party going.
Well, I like fun.
You wanna have fun? I'm in.
- No. Really?
- Yeah.
Yeah, come to Aspen.
Fuck, why not? I love Aspen. Yeah.
Want a pina colada?
Hmm. That's a lot of sugar.
Okay.
- I'll be right back.
- Okay.
Paula.
Do you need a 7 Up?
God. Guess she really does have issues.
Go help her.
Pull her hair back. Go, go, go.
She needs... Yeah.
See how it's getting in her hair?
Yeah, pull it...
Both sides, get the other side.
Yeah, there you go. Now hold on.
Paula, I'm gonna get you a 7 Up,
sweetie.
- Yes!
Hey!
The visibility was amazing.
Oh, that's great.
It was so awesome.
I could've stayed down there all day.
It wasn't weird at all.
No, it was easy. That was so cool.
Yeah, buddy!
You're right, yeah, man.
We are so lucky.
We are so lucky
to be here all together as a family.
It was really cool.
Whee!
Awesome.
Rachel.
What?
You should double bolt the door.
I told you, there's a violent criminal
running around the hotel.
The minute they arrive,
I'll have someone
bring them up to you, okay?
- Thank you.
- Bye-bye.
John, how are you?
Yes. Okay, well...
All right, but...
No, no, you told me.
Well, I have a lot to say
about this particular guest.
But, John, I...
Okay, no, that's fine.
I'll see Randy tomorrow, and we'll,
uh, we'll take it from there.
Uh, Christie,
I'm going to my office for a minute.
Okay.
Hey.
One of the guests at the spa was asking
if we had any available rooms.
- I think she's fighting with her husband.
- I don't care.
Come again?
I'm getting fired. I don't care.
You're what?
Yeah, Randy's coming tomorrow
to fire me.
Shut up.
This fucking douchebag fucker
fucked me, Belinda.
Who?
Fuck all.
Armond.
Come to my office.
Shut the door.
Or leave it open, I don't care.
Let's go hard.
Is this like a kamikaze situation?
Are you gonna take me down with you?
What do you care? You make shit money.
They exploit me. I exploit you.
Crash and burn, Dillon.
Better at your age,
before you've wasted your entire life.
Like me.
Fuck this place.
Thank you so much.
All right, girls,
we're leaving for dinner
in about 15 minutes.
Your laundry, madam.
Quinn? Time to get ready.
Yes, mother.
Come on, girls. It's our last dinner.
Feeling better?
Why are you so down?
Worried you might be going to jail?
I wouldn't be worried, though.
Unless you sent him some text
that could incriminate you.
Did you?
Your island lover
who broke into our room.
What?
Paula, cut the crap.
I mean, I didn't know
why you wouldn't tell me,
but I guess it's 'cause you were
planning some sort of heist
or something?
Are you serious?
You gave him the code to our safe.
Paula, do you think
I'm some sort of idiot?
You're making a big deal
about putting some cheap necklace
I have never seen you wear
before in the safe.
And then an hour later,
the guy you're screwing
breaks into our room
and steals all of our shit.
It's pretty basic.
It's not what you think.
Well, what is it?
It's not like I'm gonna rat you out.
Do you need money or something?
No.
No, it was never for me.
Then what is it?
I just... You won't understand.
Yes, I will. I'm not my parents, Paula.
But you are.
Actually, you are.
And you think you're like this rebel,
but in the end...
this is your tribe.
Your family, the people here.
That's really manipulative, Paula.
You're the one who stole,
yet I'm the bad guy?
Don't give me that. You've stolen, too.
What did I steal?
Well, I guess it's not stealing
when you think everything's
already yours.
Just stop pretending to be my friend.
I'm just some prop you use
for some weird cred.
Whatever you did, Paula,
it was really fucked up.
My mom could've gotten really hurt.
Something bad could've happened.
Something bad did happen.
Honey?
Thank God you're here.
You know it.
- Hey.
Hi.
Listen, I'm...
Oh, how did it go with your guy?
Good, good, yeah.
Yeah? Really?
Yeah. Actually, we're gonna go
to Honolulu tomorrow.
Yeah, spend the weekend together.
That is so nice.
Make sure to do some shopping.
I know.
And then maybe Aspen,
you know, for a couple months,
you know, see how that goes.
What? Making big moves?
Good for you, Tanya.
Anyway, we're gonna be
leaving early, and I...
I really just wanted to make sure
that I didn't miss you.
Belinda, you're an amazing person.
You are.
I mean, you've helped me so much.
I was a mess.
I showed up here, and... and somehow,
you were able
to just jumpstart my life again.
And I don't think
I'm ever gonna be functional.
But I do think that now,
I'll be able to break some old patterns.
Definitely.
Anyway, about the business...
I really need to think about it.
I mean, you're so talented
and I so wanna do this for you,
but I'm realizing I'm getting back
into this pattern again
where I latch on to somebody
and then I use my money to control them
and see, right now,
the last thing I need in my life
is another transactional relationship.
You know, it's just...
it's not healthy for me,
you know?
Anyway, I really,
I want you to know how grateful I am
and I want you to have this.
Here.
I'm gonna call you.
Okay.
My glasses... and...
This is the spa.
I gotta go.
It's my last dinner.
Something going on with that guy.
Will you leave that poor man alone?
Look, I don't know
what's going on with you exactly.
But when you stop spiraling out
and you come back to Earth,
I'll be here.
I'm here for you.
I'm your husband.
And I love you.
What is going on?
I'm sorry.
Why are you doing this?
Why are you ruining everything?
- I'm sorry.
- I mean, Jesus Christ, Rachel.
Like, are you for real right now?
What the fuck is going on?
I don't wanna go home.
Quinn.
What's wrong with home?
Everything sucks at home. It's all dead.
What are you talking about?
I just... I wanna live.
Okay. Honey,
we'll take more trips.
You know, we'll get out of the city.
No, that's not the same.
Mom, I wanna live.
We can go camping.
I mean, maybe not camping,
but, you know.
I'm going on a Hokule'a, period.
Hey, Quinn, you're 16, you're a minor.
You're still ours,
and we want you home, okay?
I think... I think it's a good idea
to get out the city more often.
You know what?
I think we should finally buy that boat.
Mark, we're not getting a boat.
No, we can be one
of those boat families.
You don't know anything
about boats, Mark.
Who's gonna steer the boat?
Obviously you, Mom.
Yeah, we could jet ski, water ski.
We can waterboard.
- Wakeboard, Dad.
- Hmm?
It's wakeboard.
Waterboard is a form of torture.
- Same thing.
- Wakeboard.
I said waterboard.
Everyone knows that... No, Mom.
So, what's the problem?
I mean, there is no problem,
everything's perfect.
Yeah, I guess.
Yeah, so, then... what?
I just feel...
When I'm with you, I feel just...
weirdly...
alone.
Uh.
Okay.
Then be alone.
I nailed dinner.
- Yeah, you!
- Yeah!
Hello, Hutch.
What's up, boss?
That was the best seating ever.
Yeah!
Double tequila.
Sure, sounds good. Coming right up.
Hey.
Greg. Greg. Water?
- All right?
- Oh, yeah, thank you. Shit.
There's something you should know.
I've had some health issues.
Like what?
It's no big deal. It's nothing.
It's just...
Don't be surprised
if I suddenly just drop dead.
Death doesn't have
to spoil everything, right?
Enjoy your life
till they drop the curtain.
Well...
I've had every kind of treatment
over the years.
Death...
is the last immersive experience
I haven't tried.
_
Hello?
Yeah, I'm still here.
Yeah, uh, why don't you
meet me in the lobby?
No problem.
My son and I are looking
for some kind of activities.
Put us in the wrong room.
Something really important
that I need to do.
Drinking on the job?
My mother's ashes.
I'm gonna need a boat.
We're supposed to have
a plunge pool on a private patio.
- You have our backpacks.
- There's stuff missing from my bag.
I have this email here from my mother.
What's it like being fucked up the ass?
We did pay more money.
Do you think we can get
another kind of upgrade?
It's just not the kind of trip
where you wanna be
impacted negatively
by someone else's mistake.
Did you find our medications?
Who's your boss? I want to talk to him.
You said you were
gonna bring me that number.
I'm calling him.
I fucked everything up.
It's okay.
I mean, I was always gonna live life
on my own terms.
Obviously.
But then what I manifested is...
pretty mediocre.
But, like,
could I live with myself
if I made this Faustian bargain
where I just ended up
being someone's arm candy
for the rest of my life?
And, you know,
I've never been the kind of person
to wanna create drama.
I don't want that.
But I know that I have to deal
with these feelings eventually.
And...
I don't know, I'm sorry.
I don't wanna burden you with this.
It's... I'm just having a moment.
I don't know. I just...
What do you think?
You want my advice?
I'm all out.
Shit.
Yeah, I have a message.
She got her own room.
That's perfect.
Thank you for letting me know.
What the...
Oh, oh, fuck. Oh, oh, fuck.
Yeah, I'm in the Pineapple Suite,
and there's a fucking turd in my room.
Somebody got in here and took a shit,
not in the toilet,
in my luggage, on my clothes.
What the fuck?
No, it isn't anyone in my party.
It wasn't me, and my wife
doesn't shit on the goddamn floor!
Someone broke in and took a dump.
Yes, send someone.
This is so fucked up!
Oh, God.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Oh, fuck. I'm...
I'm sorry.
Oh, shit.
_
Everything's fine.
I'm happy, promise.
I'll... I'll be happy.
Oh, thank God.
- Synced and corrected by Darrow -
- www.MY-SUBS.com -
_
Mossbachers!
Oh, I was hoping to catch you.
I have good news.
- They found the guy?
- They did.
What's his name?
Kai.
Paula and Olivia are in a crossroad
in their friendship.
I think that Paula
absolutely feels like,
"I don't think that you can
fully understand me
as a friend, and as a person,
and as someone who's
experiencing and seeing
things on a certain level."
To Olivia, what Paula did was wrong,
and didn't make any sense.
My mom could've gotten... really hurt.
Something bad could've happened.
Something bad did happen.
The unlikely happy ending of the show
is that Mark and Nicole end up
in a good place in their marriage
and their relationship.
This is why people go on vacation.
Even in their dysfunction,
they rely on each other so much
that I think both of them
would be lost without each other.
There is hope there, and there is love,
and you can see it.
And I was really glad that
that was part of the story.
You look at Mark and Nicole,
and ultimately,
they remain in their structure.
Quinn decides to do the opposite.
It's like a parent's greatest hope
and then, ultimately,
their worst nightmare
is that, like, this kid's gonna be free
of all of his screens
and make friends, but the friends
are gonna want to take him
on a paddle boat to Fiji.
- Hi.
You were on fire last night.
I was?
Yeah, you were hilarious.
Tanya finds Greg,
and Greg is this window into life again,
into love and romance.
But the irony is that something is not
totally healthy about Greg.
Greg...
I'm okay.
Greg is really ill, he's terminally ill.
So he doesn't sweat the details of life.
He's just going with the flow.
She ends up blowing off Belinda
because she's found the man
of her dreams.
But the man of her dreams,
how long is he gonna last?
About the business...
I really need to think about it.
The essence of who they are
is good for both of them.
But someone like Tanya's so spoiled,
she couldn't possibly understand
Belinda's hardship.
Anyway, I really... I want you to know
how grateful I am,
and I want you... to have this.
I think she's being genuine,
and because of her privilege,
she doesn't understand
that gratitude can be expressed
outside of money.
Tanya can make a mess of her life
and other people's life,
and just keep going, moving on.
Armond is definitely
partially responsible for his demise.
But it's the whole game
that these characters are playing into.
You know, that is... It creates tragedy.
Oh, God...
Oh, fuck...
Oh, fuck.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
Shane thinks there's
a violent burglar in his room,
and he's defending himself.
People do bad things in this show,
but there's no absolute villain,
and there's no absolute hero.
Everyone makes
some questionable choices,
and you get to see why they made them.
It's the manifestation
of how Armond feels about his life.
And these absurd requests,
and he ultimately dies over it.
Could I live with myself
if I made this...
Faustian bargain,
where I just ended up
being someone's arm-candy
for the rest of my life?
You want my advice?
I'm all out.
For Belinda, there is some resentment.
Like, "You can wipe your tears away
with a Louis Vuitton handkerchief,
and that is something
that I can't really give you
any shoulder to cry on about."
You always have more options
when you have money,
and that helps propel Rachel back
into the relationship.
The lifestyle that Shane provides her,
ultimately, is more seductive
than her own self-respect.
I'm happy, I promise.
I'll... I'll be happy.
I think there's a real sadness
to their story,
and you can see the writing on the wall,
and see that this girl is, ultimately,
not going to be happy,
but doesn't know what to do about it.
It's a very fraught time in the culture,
as far as gender and race and class,
and I felt like, if we're gonna do
a contemporary show,
we need to touch on all of those ideas
and have a diverse group of viewpoints.
_